

Kuala Lumpur +61 415 298 253

### **PROFILE**

### PERSONAL STATEMENT

Name: Nur Aisyah binti Mohd Hanifiah Date of Birth: 16 April 1996 I find joy in creating visuals that are able to engage with people effectively while fulfilling the aesthetics of each graphic element. I do work well both as a member of a team and in isolation with high attention to detail. Based on my past experiences being a graphic designer, I learnt a lot about how each graphics and type could influence the viewers. It is that everywhere I go I would think to myself on how people could improve their marketing materials.

## EXPERIENCE

### FREELANCE GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Amber & Sparkles | Sept 2016 - Dec 2016

- https://www.instagram.com/amberandsparkles/
- Creating graphics based on tasks given and meeting deadlines

### FREELANCE GRAPHIC DESIGNER

The Pixel Things | August 2016 - current

- Founder of The Pixel Things (Instagram: @thepixelthings)
- Manage projects, customers and meeting deadlines

### INDUSTRIAL TRAINING

Motive Interactive Sdn, Bhd. | Feb 2017 - Jun 2017

- Assist in software development cycles for current projects
- Developed personal project using Laravel PHP framework

## **EDUCATION**

### BACHELOR IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

University of Queensland | Jun 2018 - current

# DIPLOMA IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Universiti Kuala Lumpur (MIIT) | Jun 2014 - Jun 2017

Pure science

CGPA: 3.97

### SIJIL PELAJARAN MALAYSIA

Sekolah Tun Fatimah | 2009-2013

Pure science

Grade: 5A+ 4A

## SKILLS

Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator PHP HTML & CSS WordPress Bootstrap MySQL

# **KNOWLEDGE**

JAVA C# C++ VB.NET ASP.NET

# PERSONAL SKILLS

TEAMWORK	
CREATIVITY	_
ORGANIZATION	
COMMUNICATION	
INDEPENDENT	

# REFERENCES

Private information disclosed

# LANGUAGE SKILLS

Malay

English